本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译：  小犀 红鼻子的UFO 黑色风车 猫 Vernie
校对： cinderella   后期： 泡面小小
东区女巫前情提要
Previously on Witches of East End
起作用了! 等等 别消失啊
It worked! Wait. Don't go away.
我太笨了
I suck at this.
阿奇博尔德・布朗宁
Archibald Browning.
在二十世纪初建立了这个地方
The man who built this place back in the early 1900s.
你只不过杀死了我的大女儿
You only killed my eldest daughter.
英格丽德已经重生了
Ingrid was reborn.
记着 我认识你已经好几个世纪了
Remember, I've known you for over several centuries,
你可能是我们中最有天赋的一个
and you're probably the most gifted one of us all.
我们的族类必须服从一点
All of our kind must abide.
我们决不泄漏我们的身份
We never reveal ourselves.
我将成为你的嫂子
I'm going to be your sister-in-law,
我希望你和我的丈夫...
and I want you and my husband...
我不能看着你和他在一起
I can't watch you with him.
基利安!
Killian!
酒吧里的电路出了故障
The electrical system at the bar went haywire.
只是做我的本职工作而已
Just doing my job.
秘密是恋爱中的毒药 你说对吗?
Secrets are poison in a relationship, don't you agree?
- 嗨 - 天啊...
- Hey. - Oh, my God...
你在这做什么?
What are you doing here?
- 游泳啊 - 哦
- Swimming. - Yeah.
- 这个我知道 - 漂亮又聪明
- That much I can figure out. - Beauty and brains.
真是完美啊
Quite the combination.
告诉我 你一直这么自以为是吗?
Tell me something. Have you always been a smart-ass?
差不多
Pretty much.
说真的 你在我的游泳池里做什么?
Seriously, what are you doing in my pool?
佩内洛普说我可以随意用她的游泳池
Penelope said I could use her pool whenever I want.
这比冰冷的海水好多了 所以...
It beats the freezing cold ocean, so...
你叫她佩内洛普?
You call her Penelope?
你知道这有点奇怪 对吧?
You know that's really weird, right?
她是你妈妈啊
She's your mom.
真的吗? 现在听起来你更像我妈妈
Really? 'Cause right now it sounds like you're my mom.
那么 你以后会经常来这了?
So, does this mean you come here often?
这是搭讪吗? 你在勾引我?
Is that a line? Are you trying to pick up on me?
拜托 想得美
Please. You wish.
你说的对 我确实想
You're right. I do.
我希望你以后不那么说话
Uh... I wish you wouldn't say things like that.
拜托 我只是开个玩笑
Come on, I'm just messing around.
我知道 我...
I know. I...
不只是这个 我... 我觉得你好像在等我
It's not just that, I... I feel like you're waiting for me or something.
我不希望你那样
And I don't want you to.
我没有等啊
I'm not waiting.
但是我听见你的话了 一清二楚
But I hear you, loud and clear.
我记得你的医生还不允许你游泳
I don't recall your doctor giving you permission to swim yet.
我很好
Uh, I'm fine.
上周你刚刚被电击过呢
Well, you suffered a profound electric shock last week.
但我觉得好像我有了几千块钱一样
And yet I feel like a thousand bucks.
好吧 那不算很多钱 基利安
Yeah. That's not a lot of money, Killian.
- 是啊 对你来说不算 - 你知道吗?
- Well, maybe not to you. - But you know what?
我希望你下午来趟医院 我要给你复查
I'd like you to come by the hospital this afternoon so I can take a look at you.
- 一点 怎么样? - 好的 老爸
- Say... 1:00? - 'Kay, Dad.
你们两个和好了?
So, you guys are just cool now?
不 还没有
No, not really.
但是 这么多年我一直很想他
But, like, I've missed him all these years, and if there's a way
即使让我们达到正常关系的一半
we can even have a halfway normal relationship,
我也会尝试的
I might as well try.
还能怎么样? 毕竟他是我弟弟啊
What can I say? He's my little brother.
你是我见过的最好的人
You know, you are the best person I've ever met.
- 最好的? - 最好的
- The best? - The best.
英格丽德・波尚
Ingrid Beauchamp.
加德纳夫人!
Mrs. Gardiner!
我正好在找你
Just the woman I wanted to see.
需要我帮你找什么书吗?
Can I help you with a book?
不用 我给你带了件礼物
No, but I've come bearing gifts for you.
你知道 费尔黑文正在重修
As you know, renovations at Fair Haven have been ongoing,
我找到了一些以前的宝贝
and we've unearthed quite a few gems from the past.
- 哦... - 有一样特别的东西...
- Oh... - One in particular...
我觉得你会感兴趣
I thought you'd be interested in.
这简直...
Wow. That's...
不可思议吧?
Uncanny, right?
我看到的时候简直不敢相信
I could hardly believe it when I saw it.
她和你一模一样 英格丽德
She looks exactly like you, Ingrid.
有点吧 我觉得眼睛有点像
A little, I guess, around the eyes.
她可能是你的双胞胎姐妹呢
She could be your twin.
这个女人一定是你的亲戚 你觉得呢?
This woman must have been a relative of yours, don't you think?
绝对的
Definitely. Yes.
我家已经在这住很久了
I know my family has lived in this town
所以这很有可能
for a long time, so that would make sense.
我很好奇她是谁
I wonder who she was.
还有她看起来为什么这么忧虑
And why she looks so troubled.
你觉得她看起来很忧虑?
You think she looks troubled?
是的
I do.
东区女巫 第一季第06集
- 好的 记住我教你的 - 好的
- All right, remember what I taught you. - Right.
深呼吸... 设定目标...
Deep breath... Set your intention...
然后释放出来
And let it out.
- 天啊! 我做到了! - 你做到了!
- Holy crap! I did it! - You did it!
我真为你自豪
I am so proud of you.
你达到一个新的水平了
You're at a whole another level with this stuff.
是啊 太不可思议了
I know. It's incredible.
就像... 我突然变强了
It's like I'm... Suddenly stronger.
我觉得我对生活更有掌控力了
And I feel more in control of my life.
我告诉基利安要向前看
I told Killian to move on.
我做到了! 而且当时他没穿衣服
I did! And he was shirtless at the time,
所以你知道我有多厉害了吧
so you know I meant it.
他为什么没穿衣服?
Why was he shirtless?
我们当时在泳池里 思想别那么龌龊
We were in the pool. Get your mind out of the gutter.
好的 祝你好运
Okay. Good for you.
现在好像没有什么我做不到的了
It's like there's nothing I can't do right now.
你能灭火吗? 因为你刚刚点火了
Can you put out fires? 'Cause I think you started one.
也许我太强了?
Maybe I'm too powerful?
是的 那... 对 你就是那样
Yeah. That... yeah, that's what you are.
我们该怎么办?
What are we gonna do?
我认为我们没什么要做的
Well, I don't think there's anything we can do.
如果她发现那是我呢?
What if she figures out it's me?
英格丽德 我想没人会因为
Ingrid. I don't think anyone's
看了那张百年老照
gonna look at that hundred-year-old photograph
就觉得你是一个巫师
and decide that it means you're a secret witch
会因为一个古老的咒语而不断地重生
under an ancient curse that causes you to be reborn
你也说了 她认为那是个亲戚
You said it yourself. She assumed it's a relative.
怎么了?
What's going on?
佩内洛普找到了一张
Uh, Penelope found an old photograph
英格丽德在费尔黑文的老照片
of Ingrid at Fair Haven.
你是担心她会认出你来吗?
Oh. And you're worried she's gonna figure out it's you?
睡衣不错哦
Cool bathing suit.
我不知道 只是 我知道那是我
I don't know. It's just, I know that it's me,
但是我不知道我其他轮回的任何事
but I don't know anything about my other lives,
我有点好奇
and I'm starting to get curious.
- 哦 - 是的
- Oh. - Yeah.
和我在一起的那个小女孩是谁?
Who is that little girl I'm with?
为什么我会在费尔黑文?
Why was I hanging out at Fair Haven?
我认识阿奇博尔德・布朗宁吗?
Did I know Archibald Browning?
不怎么认识 这... 没什么...
Not really. It's... not really...
- 值得深究的 - 没错
- Worth getting into that. - No.
我知道肯定不仅如此
I can tell there's more to this.
为什么你们不想让我知道?
Why don't you want me to know?
我不想你被你的前世所限
I don't want you to be defined by all your other lives.
我不想你背负着前世的罪过
I don't want you to carry the baggage of all your mistakes.
什么罪过?!
What mistakes?!
好吧 别告诉我
Fine. Don't tell me.
她不会死心的
She's not gonna stop.
你知道她有多固执 我们应该告诉她真相吗?
You know how determined she is. Should we just tell her the truth?
如果我们告诉她 她也许永远不会原谅你
If we tell her, she may never forgive you.
你真想冒那个险吗?
You really want to risk that?
好的 深吸气
All right, big breath in.
呼气
Out.
好了
All right.
还不错 不过你还要进行全面的血液检查
Sounds good. But you should have a full blood panel done.
我有点怀念你的说教了
I oddly miss these lectures.
像以前一样
Feels like old times.
想回到以前 还需要很多努力
You got a long way to go before it's like old times again.
但是... 看到你差点没命
But... seeing you almost die
确实让情况乐观了不少
did put things in perspective.
向我保证你会去检查 好吗?
Just promise me you'll get a checkup, all right?
不如我保证不再被电击吧?
How about if I just promise not to get electrocuted again?
成交吗?
Deal?
加德纳医生?
Dr. Gardiner?
我对你从莫拉・撒切尔嗓子里拿出来的东西
I ran some tests
做了些测试
on the mass you pulled from Maura Thatcher's throat.
它似乎是由有机海绵状骨组织组成的
It appears to be made of some sort of organic, spongy osseous tissue.
但是我了解到 它...
But get this, it...
天哪 我没有发现还有病人在这 我很抱歉
Oh, God, I didn't realize you had a patient in here. I am so sorry.
不 没关系 我们结束了
No, no, it's okay. We're finished.
艾米 这是我的弟弟 基利安
Amy, this is my brother, Killian.
基利安 这是马修斯医生
Killian, Dr. Matthews, MD,
博士 医学研究的超级巨星
PhD, medical research superstar.
我们等会再说吧
Um, we can finish this later.
别介意我在这
Oh, hey, don't leave 'cause of me.
我很喜欢这个有机海绵状骨组织的故事
I love a good organic, spongy, osseous tissue story.
谁会不喜欢呢?
Oh. Well, who doesn't?
我不知道加德纳医生还有一个弟弟
So, I didn't know Dr. Gardiner had a brother.
是啊 他喜欢低调行事 可我就出现了
Yeah, he likes to keep that quiet. But here I am.
对啊 干得好
Yep, and here you go.
我还有工作要做
I've got work to do.
很糟糕 今天你不是我唯一的病人
Shockingly, you're not my only patient today.
- 真的很高兴见到你 艾米 - 我也是
- Really nice to meet you, Amy. - You, too. Yeah.
这怎么可能...
How is that possible...
英格丽德 猜发生了什么?
Ingrid, guess what?
你在干嘛呢?
Oh. What are you doing?
- 刨根问底 - 这是什么意思?
- Falling down the rabbit hole. - What do you mean?
佩内洛普找到这张我在费尔黑文的照片
Penelope found this picture of me at Fair Haven,
和我在一起的这个小女孩看起来异常亲切
and I'm with this little girl who looks strangely familiar,
但老妈不肯告诉我她是谁 你也知道她
but Mom won't tell me who it is; you know how she gets
一向对过去守口如瓶 所以我想
about the past, so I thought,
我不需要老妈
hey, I don't need Mom,
我是个研究员... 我就做一些研究吧
I'm a researcher... I'll just do some research.
然后我弄明白了它是雅典娜
And that's how I figured out it was Athena.
谁是雅典娜?
What was Athena?
照片里的小女孩是雅典娜・布朗宁
The little girl in the picture was Athena Browning.
阿奇博尔德家的人
As in Archibald.
你知道吧 那个建立费尔黑文的男人
You know, the man who built Fair Haven.
- 撒旦教 邪教领袖 - 我不明白
- Satanist, cult leader. - Yeah, I don't get it.
雅典娜是阿奇博尔德的女儿 你有水吗?
Athena is Archibald's daughter. Do you have any water?
我好渴啊 这还很押韵呢
I'm really thirsty. And that rhymed.
英格丽德 这布朗尼蛋糕里
Ingrid, is there anything else
除了巧克力还放了什么东西?
in these brownies besides chocolate?
完全正确!
Exactly!
- 这就是关键! - 什么是关键?
- That is the point! - What is the point?
所有努力的关键 努力跟上我的思路
Of the entire endeavor. Try to keep up.
当我发现这小女孩是谁时
See, when I realized who the little girl was,
我想 见鬼 这和我有什么关系
I thought, holy shit, what does this have to do with me,
...为什么老妈不想让我知道?
...and why doesn't Mom want me to know?
我是个女巫啊 我只用念一段咒语
I'm a witch; I'll just cast a spell.
一个帮我恢复记忆的咒语 我查找了魔法书
A spell to help me remember So I searched the Grimoire,
然后找到了这个配方 虽然我有点搞砸了
and I found this recipe, which I messed with a little,
但之后我成功了...
and then I did it...
一个帮我记起1906年的生活
a spell to help me remember
的咒语... 我把它烤到这布朗尼蛋糕里了
my life from 1906... I baked it into this brownie.
- 然后呢? - 我很肯定是骗人的
- And? - I'm pretty sure it's bunk.
我把整盘的蛋糕都吃了 我没有任何感觉
I've eaten the entire pan. I don't really feel a thing,
除了有点小激动 你想尝一块试试吗?
except I'm a little agitated.
看这对你有没有用
Do you want to try one, see if it works on you?
不用了! 谢谢 这挺诱人的
No! No. Thank you. That's tempting.
但我要去见达什
But I'm gonna meet Dash,
然后我会去上班
and then I'm gonna go to work.
- 好吧 - 你要告诉我之后如何 好吗?
- Okay. - You let me know how that goes, okay?
真是一点帮助也没有啊 魔法布朗尼
Thanks for nothing, magic brownie.
英格丽德
Ingrid.
你是我见过的最美的尤物
You are the most beautiful creature I have ever seen.
我爱你 阿奇博尔德
I love you, Archibald.
这些测试结果肯定是错的
Okay, these test results can't be right.
我也是这么认为的
I didn't think so either.
所以我重复测试了 无数次
So I ran them again. And again and again...
你确定组织样本没有被污染吗?
Are you sure the tissue sample wasn't compromised?
我要装作没听见你刚才的问题
I'm gonna pretend like you didn't just ask me that question.
我没有质疑你 这些测试结果不科学啊
It's not you I'm questioning. These test results are unscientifically possible.
我在一本名不见经传的医学杂志上
Well, I did find an example of a similar phenomenon
找到一例相似的现象
in an obscure medical journal.
似乎 在1995年 路易斯安那州的乡村
Apparently, in 1995, a woman in rural Louisiana
一名喉咙疼痛 呼吸困难的女子到
presented in a small county E.R. with severe throat pain
小镇急症室
and obstructed breathing.
他们发现这东西生长在她的气管里
They found one of these growing out of her windpipe.
这是先天性的吗?
And it was idiopathic?
是的 尽管她声称这是因为她被女巫诅咒过
Yep. Although she claims it was because she was cursed by a voodoo priestess.
或许我们可以联系那个医院
Okay, maybe we should contact that hospital
相互参照下我们的发现
and cross-reference our findings.
我们不能 因为
We can't. Get this.
在这件事发生三周后 医生和两名研究员
The admitting doctor and two researchers all died
都因为严重的肺部感染而死
of severe lung infections three weeks after the incident.
医院也被捣毁了
The hospital was demolished due
因为明显的石棉污染
to an apparent asbestos contamination.
样本也永远无法复原了
The sample was never recovered.
- 这还真没帮助啊 - 是啊
- Well, that's not very helpful. - No.
你好
Hello.
我可以进来吗?
Can I come in?
- 嗨 宝贝 - 弗雷娅 很高兴见到你
- Hey, babe. - Freya, so good to see you.
那是什么东西啊?
Hi. What is that thing?
那是医学未解之谜
That is a medical mystery.
但我会解开谜团的
But I'm gonna solve it.
它是从哪来的?
Where'd it come from?
那天莫拉・撒切尔在弯曲手肘对你们大叫以后
Oh, I pulled it out of Maura Thatcher's throat
我从她的嗓子里拿出来的
the day she freaked out on your family at the Bent Elbow.
是吗?
You did?
或许她被女巫诅咒了呢
Hey, maybe she was cursed by a voodoo priestess.
什么?!
What?!
她开玩笑的 我们为什么不休息一下呢?
She's kidding. Look, why don't we take a break?
要不我们去吃午餐吧?
Maybe we should grab some lunch?
- 好啊 - 好
- Yeah, sure. - Okay.
不
Oh, no.
阿奇博尔德
Archibald.
我又收到弗雷娅的信了!
I got another letter from Freya!
她在旧金山定居了
She's settled in San Francisco
她还说找到了这辈子的真爱
and says she's met the love of her life.
- 还有什么新鲜事? - 我好想她啊
- What else is new? - Oh, I miss her so.
伊迪丝 告诉我你的症状
Edith, tell me what the problem is.
我的手很酸 我都抬不起来了
My hands are so sore I can barely lift 'em.
我怕再也用不了这手了
And I'm afraid they'll never work again.
别担心
Well, not to worry.
温迪会给你调配适合的药膏
Wendy will mix you just the right salve.
现在 闭上眼睛  伊迪丝
And in the meantime, close your eyes, Edith.
妈咪嘛咪哄
Sana manus mulieris huius.
老天
Oh, my.
感觉好多了
It's much better.
好神奇
Like... magic.
这是我在欧洲学的一点医治疗法
It's just a little healing technique I picked up in Europe.
伊迪丝 这是擦手的软膏 一天擦两次
Edith, this is the ointment that you rub on your hands twice daily.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
你们三个真是创造奇迹的人
You three really are miracle-workers.
谢谢你 伊迪丝
Thank you, Edith.
乔安娜...
Joanna...
气色不错嘛
You're looking well.
这要两美元
That'll be two dollars.
还有一件事
Oh, uh, one more thing.
我有个门徒生病了
One of my disciples has fallen ill.
我在找一种草药 它叫热狐
I'm looking for an herb. It's called feverfox.
我从没听过这草药
I've never heard of it.
我记得我在你的货架上见到过
Hmm. I believe I've seen it here on your shelves.
它是... 它是一种蓝色的粉末
It's a... it's a bluish powder.
对 我姐说的没错 我们没有库存热狐
No. My sister's right. We don't stock feverfox.
它是非法的 用不好就会有剧毒
It's illegal and rather toxic in the wrong hands.
我以为你从来没听说过它呢
Hmm. I thought you'd never heard of it.
她没听过 我听过
She hasn't. I have.
我们没法帮你
We can't help you.
没关系
Of course.
那我走了
Well, I'll be going, then.
女士们你们真应该去费尔黑文看看
You ladies really must pay a visit to Fair Haven.
它终于建完了 我想你们会被我们的成果打动
It's finally complete, and I think you'll be impressed with what we're doing.
它是我们另一种层次的存在
It is the next level of being for our kind.
- 不了 谢谢你 - 我们很好
- No, thank you. - We're good.
但愿如此
As you wish.
英格丽德?
Ingrid?
见到你真好
Good to see you.
嘿 怎么了?
Hey, what's up?
我们应该担心这玩意儿吗?
Should we be worried about this?
你从哪儿拿到的?
Where did you get that?
在医院 怎么了? 这是什么东西?
At the hospital. Why? What is it?
枝毒 死亡树枝 碰到就会死
Ramus mortium, branch of death. You touch it, you die.
什么?
What?
万一已经晚了呢?
What if it's too late?
枝毒病毒需要几周的时间才能侵入体内
Ramus mortium sickness takes a few weeks to kick in.
所以我们还有时间 我们能治好
So we have time. We'll fix it.
要是侵入了会怎么样?
And when it does kick in?
你知道那种湿乎乎的金属性的东西
You know that, uh, drippy metallicy stuff
- 也是树枝的一部分吗? - 是的
- that was on the branch? - Yeah. Uh-huh.
它会缓慢而坚定地注入到你的肺里
That slowly but surely fills up your lungs
直至你窒息而死
until you drown from within.
- 你为什么告诉我这些? - 你问的啊
- Why would you tell me that? - You asked.
那也没必要回答得这么直白嘛
You didn't have to answer that honestly.
天那 都怪你 是你对莫拉施的咒
Oh, my God. This is all your fault. You were the one that put the spell on Maura.
不 不 不 我使不出这么阴险毒辣的招数
No, no, no. This is something much bigger, much darker.
我觉得是假冒者袭击她的时候干的
I bet it happened when the shifter attacked her.
那为什么莫拉能从如此的剧毒下死里逃生?
So why isn't Maura dead if this thing is so toxic?
她是寄主 它在体内生长 所以她有免疫
She's the host. It grew from within, so she's immune.
而你正相反...
You on the other hand...
我知道 我是被感染的
Oh, yeah, I know. I'm infected.
好吧 弗雷娅 我需要你好好听我说
Okay, Freya, I'm gonna need you to listen to me.
我不会骗你
I'm not gonna lie to you.
患上枝毒病很严重 非常严重
Ramus mortium sickness is bad. Really bad.
我见过死于这病的人 在三百年前
I've seen people die from it. I've seen you die from it
我还见过你死于此病 所以我需要你振作起来
300 years ago, so I'm gonna need you to suck it up.
哇哦 这真是世上最扯的鼓励了
Wow. This is the world's shittiest pep talk.
我的意思是你不一定会死
My point is you don't have to die from it.
那时候我们不知道怎么治 但现在我们有办法
We didn't know how to stop it back then. We do now.
这药水就可以治愈 我需要你来制作
This drink is the cure. I'm gonna need you to make it.
但为什么是我?
But why me?
亲爱的 尽管你毫无经验
Honey, even with all your inexperience,
但你有使用药剂的天赋
you have a gift for potions.
这是与生俱来的
It's in your blood.
我永远赶不上你在这方面的能耐
I'm never gonna be able to make it as good as you.
这个树枝也能杀死普通人吗?
So this branch can kill regular people, too?
任何碰到它的人
Anybody who touches it.
但这个解药可以在几年内提供保护
But this antidote offers protection for a few years...
就像是破伤风针... 防止再次感染
It's kind of like a tetanus shot... Just in case you're re-exposed.
所以达什和艾米也得服用
So I'm gonna have to get Dash and Amy to take this, too.
是 一定要让他们喝得多多的 好吗?
Yes. And make sure they drink a lot, okay?
当你耳鸣的时候就说明你痊愈了
You'll know that you're cured when your ears start ringing.
- 弗雷娅? - 啥?
- Freya? - Huh?
作为一个给力的女巫 你是在拯救生命
You're gonna save lives, like the ass-kicking witch that you are.
好的
Okay.
"你看他的父母
"Interruption to his father and mother,
他们这般为他忍耐着 是多么耐心而善良啊"
how patiently and kindly so ever they might endure it for his sake..."
- 英格丽德! - 雅典娜！
- Ingrid! - Athena!
你没来吃晚饭 你说过要给我编辫子
You missed dinner. And you said you were going to braid my hair.
我知道 我实在走不开
I know. I couldn't get away.
抱歉 我明天给你编吧
I'm sorry, but I'll braid it tomorrow.
- 保证? - 嗯
- Promise? - Mm-hmm.
准备睡觉吧 亲爱的
Go get ready for bed, dear.
- 晚安 老爸 - 晚安 英格丽德
- Good night, Daddy. - Good night, Ingrid.
你今天很有说服力呢
You were very convincing today.
我差点儿以为你不认识我
I almost believed you didn't know me.
那怎么可能
That would be an unthinkable reality.
你带来热狐了吗?
Did you bring the feverfox?
好姑娘
Good girl.
卡利俄铂! 带伊丽莎白进来！
Calliope! Fetch Elizabeth!
伊丽莎白 很高兴你决定面对这些
Elizabeth, I'm glad you decided to go through with this.
你不会后悔的
You won't regret it.
我得承认我有点儿紧张
Oh, I must admit I'm a little nervous.
我哥哥以为你们是魔鬼
My brother thinks you all do the devil's work.
你哥哥是白痴
Your brother is a cretin.
英格丽德和我超越凡人
Ingrid and myself are superior creatures.
我们愿意和你们这类人来往是你的福气
You're lucky we're willing to deal with your kind at all,
更何况我们还帮你
let alone help you the way we are.
我看到 你把钱带来了
I see you've, uh, brought the money.
这是我全部家当了
This is everything I have.
我不想说谎
I'm not going to lie.
这个... 会疼的
This... will hurt.
很疼
A lot.
谢谢你
Thank you.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes
然后喝下去
and drink.
妈咪嘛咪哄
Spiritus obscuri da viriditatum.
奏效了吗?
Did it work?
奏效了 你又年轻了
It did. You are young again.
你如愿以偿了
You have what you wanted.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
永生永世感激不尽
I'm forever in your debt.
卡利俄铂 今晚的仪式在泳池举行
Calliope, tonight's ritual will take place in the pool.
帮伊丽莎白准备入会
Prepare Elizabeth for her initiation.
我保证你会喜欢 亲爱的
I promise you'll love it, dear.
我们也可以... 准备了吗?
Shall we... prepare, as well?
- 谁准备好迎接下一轮啦? - 哦
- So, who's ready for another round? - Oh.
你又忘了准备我那杯
Once again, you forget a glass for me.
你还是喝你的根汁汽水吧
You stick to your root beer.
你可是我们指定的司机
You're our designated driver.
你们一群人都想坐我摩托车?
Ah, you guys all want to pile onto my motorcycle?
我说了你可以开我的车
I said you could use my car.
谢谢你今晚约我出来 弗雷娅
Thank you for inviting me out tonight, Freya,
但我可告诉你 我还不太擅长
but I have to tell you, I am a bit of an amateur,
我不知道我再喝一杯还能不能受得了
and I don't know if I can handle another one of these, um...
这叫什么来着?
What are they called?
东区解药... 带花样的
East End Antidote... with a twist.
对 是的 喝完前三轮我已经醉得不行了
Right. Yeah, I'm pretty drunk from the last three rounds.
- 胡说! 我们是在庆祝诶！ - 什么?
- Hogwash! We are celebrating! - What?
你刚才真的说了"胡说"?
Did you really just say "hogwash"?
好吧 等一下 我们在庆祝什么?
Okay, wait. What are we celebrating?
我们在庆祝你俩将会
We are celebrating the fact that you two are about
解决你们之前在研究的医学难题
to solve that whole medical mystery you were working on earlier.
其他医生怎么说?
What do the other doctors say?
还有谁跟你们一起研究?
Who else is working on it with you?
也许我们应该把他们也叫来
Maybe we should invite them here,
进行一局头脑风暴怎么样?
maybe have a little brainstorming session?
哇哦 我觉得自打我认识你以来
Wow. I think this is the most interest
这是第一次你对我的工作这么感兴趣
you've shown in my work since the day I met you.
嘿 这么说可不公平
Hey, that's not fair.
我一直对你的工作感兴趣
I'm always interested in your work.
慢着 慢着 我不是这意思 好吗?
Hold on, hold on. I didn't mean it like that, all right?
我只是说 我的工作会让人感到有压力
All I meant was, is that my job can be stressful,
我希望你这片绿洲可以远离我沙漠般的工作
and I like that you are an oasis away from all that.
这样我跟你在一起的时候
Okay, when I'm with you,
就可以忘记烦恼开开心心的
I can be happy and just forget about my troubles.
但你知道我关心你的工作啊
But you know that I care about your work.
我知道你关心
I know you do.
而你又经常什么都不说
And you don't always want to talk about it.
你说得对 我经常闷着
You're right. I don't.
抱歉 我不应该这样
I'm sorry. It just came out wrong.
这是我喝过的最美味的饮料
This is the most delicious drink I think I've ever had.
它 它的味道像... 阳光
It, um... it tastes like... sunshine.
- 哇哦 - 确实像！
- Wow. - It does!
好吧 让我试试 给我尝一口
All right, let me see. Give me a sip.
- 怎么样? - 你说得对 阳光的味道
- Hmm? - You're right. Sunshine.
别这样 别生气了
Come on, don't be mad.
- 我没那意思 - 我知道 我只是...
- I didn't mean anything by it. - I know. I just...
你知道我不只能让你忘记烦心事 对吗?
You know I'm not just here to take your mind off things, right?
我不希望你对我隐藏
I mean, I don't want you to be hiding your problems from me.
不管你说的是什么 我都可以接受
I can handle it, whatever it is you want to throw at me.
我知道 我希望我的生命里你无处不在
I know. I want you to be a part of everything in my life.
很好 我也是这么想的
Good, 'cause that's what I want, too.
那真是太好了
All right then.
- 嫁给我吧 - 什么?
- So marry me. - What?
我以为你们已经结婚了呢
I thought you guys were already getting married.
看吧? 艾米不愧是博士呢
See? Amy does have a PhD.
不 不 我们这周末结婚吧
No, no, marry me this weekend.
我们两个在法院结婚
At the courthouse just the two of us.
没有麻烦 没有父母 没有客人
All right, no hassle, no mothers-in-law, no guest list.
就我们两个 你们两个可以当见证人
Just us. You two can be the witnesses.
太好了!
Hell, yes!
- 好浪漫啊! - 是啊 祝福你们
- That is so romantic! - Yeah. Congratulations.
佩内洛普要高兴死啦
Penelope's gonna lose her shit.
- 干杯 - 干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
酒吧要打烊了！最后一轮！
It's last call, people! One more round!
天哪 想不到都这么晚了
Wow. I can't believe it's already last call.
- 我们接着去庆祝吧 - 好啊
- We got to keep this party going. - Yeah.
我们回费尔黑文庆祝吧?
Who wants to go back to Fair Haven and celebrate?
走吧
Let's go.
- 就这么办 - 好的
- Let's do this. - Yeah.
干杯
Cheers.
我们应该加入他们 我可以去游泳
We should join the others. I could use a swim.
我知道 只是有时候我想独占你
I know. I just like having you to myself sometimes.
只要你跟你的家人讲出事实
You can have me whenever you want
你随时都可以占有我
as soon as you tell your family the truth.
告诉他们你爱我 你愿意做我的妻子
That you love me and you're going to be my wife.
他们永远都不会理解
They will never understand.
他们会认为你给我下咒语了 我在受你的摆布
They'll think you spelled me, that I'm under your control.
好像我真能控制你似的 你比我更强大
Hmm. As if I could control you. You're more powerful than I am.
他们真的知道你有多强大吗?
Do they really not know how strong you are?
他们知道 但是他们也相信
They know, but they also believe
你是一个纯粹的恶魔
you're pure evil.
那你是怎么想的呢?
Hmm. And what do you think?
我觉得在没遇到你之前
I believe I was sleepwalking
我一直在梦游 是你把我唤醒的
before I met you, and you woke me up.
当时机到来的时候
And when the time is right,
我们将会有足够的跟随者
and we have enough followers to our cause,
我们可以回到我们的家乡
we can return to where we came from
夺回属于我们的东西
and take back what is rightfully ours.
那时我会自豪的以妻子的身份站在你旁边
And I will be proud to stand beside you as your wife,
再也不会感到羞耻
and I will not be ashamed.
英格丽德 我们两个一起
Together, Ingrid,
没有什么是做不到的
there's nothing we can't do.
伊丽莎白出事了!
Something's wrong with Elizabeth!
她不停地抖动 然后...
She just started shaking, and then...
然后就开始吐血了!
and then, all this blood started pouring out!
我不知道出什么事了！
I don't know what happened!
我们要想想办法
We need to do something.
我妈妈可以帮忙 她是个出色的医生
My mother can help. She's an excellent healer.
我们什么也做不了 她已经死了
There's nothing to be done. She's dead.
可怜的女人
Oh, poor woman.
这就是帮助一个劣等生物的结果
This is what we get for trying to help an inferior creature.
他们会怪罪我们 这会毁了我们的
They'll blame us. This could ruin everything.
要赶紧处理掉她的尸体
We need to get rid of her body.
可以把她埋在地下墓穴里
We can bury her down in the catacombs.
那些不理解我们的人 他们很快会找来的
They'll be after us now, the ones who don't understand,
但是我们可以把这看成新的开始
but we can make this a new beginning.
- 今晚 我们今晚结婚吧 - 好的
- Tonight. Let's marry tonight. - Yes.
伊丽莎白在哪儿?
Where is Elizabeth?!
伊丽莎白?
Elizabeth?
伊丽莎白?!
Elizabeth?!
你怎么进来的?
How did you get in?
你们对她做了什么?
What have you done with her?
你没权利来这儿 走吧 你妹妹很好
You have no right to be here. Be gone. Your sister is fine.
那就让我见她
Then show her to me.
你妹妹有权单独留下来
You sister has a right to be left alone.
这个镇的好人们在盯着你的一举一动
Oh. The good people of this town are on to you.
我们知道你做些恶毒的事
We know you're doing the devil's work.
你根本不知道你在说什么 赶紧走吧
You have no idea what you're talking about. You need to leave.
好啊
Fine.
我要带着我妹妹一起走
Then I will take my sister with me,
否则我就带二十个人来这里 强行把她带走
or I will return with 20 men, and we will take her ourselves.
伊丽莎白已经死了
Elizabeth is dead.
她想变年轻
She wanted to be young.
我满足了她的愿望 但是出问题了
I granted her wish. It didn't work out.
你杀了她?!
You killed her?!
那是一场不幸的转变事故
It was an unfortunate turn of events.
你现在要杀了我吗?
And now you're going to kill me?
我没有要杀你的想法
I have no intention of killing you.
我未来的妻子会杀了你
My soon-to-be-wife will do it.
阿奇博尔德?
Archibald?
就当是结婚礼物吧
Think of it as a wedding gift.
我...
I...
求你了
Please.
你让我失望了 英格丽德
You disappoint me, Ingrid.
天哪! 好冷啊
Ooh, wow. Whoa! It's freezing.
液体升温
Calor Aqua.
我感觉有点暖呢
Feels kind of warm to me.
温度肯定快达到零点了
Huh. Must have been in a cold spot or something.
那饮料让我感觉不对劲
Oh! That drink really did a number on me.
- 我有点耳鸣 - 我也是
- My ears are ringing. - Me, too.
我也是 很好 那证明起作用了
Me, too. That's good. It means it's working.
- 你在说什么? - 没什么啦
- What are you talking about? - Nothing.
我喜欢这间房子 真是...
I love this room. It's so...
吓人吗?
Creepy?
- 你认为呢? - 绝对吓人
- You think? - Oh, definitely creepy.
他们以前在这举行邪恶的性仪式
They used to have Satanic sex rituals here, you know.
好吧 说点更吓人的 工人们
All right, you want creepy. You know, the workers
在这个房子下面发现了去地下墓室的入口
just found an entrance to some catacombs underneath the house.
我还没验证过呢
I haven't even checked that out yet.
刺激 我们去看看吧
Oh, cool. Let's go.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
- 我不知道你在这儿 - 别这样
- I didn't think you were here. - Don't do this.
别干什么? 我只是拿点东西
Don't do what? I'm just getting some things.
我要去趟旧金山 去看弗雷娅
I'm taking a trip to visit Freya in San Francisco.
你穿着婚纱
You're wearing a wedding dress.
是的 但这不是你看起来的那样
Yes, but it's not what it looks like.
英格丽德 别这样
Ingrid, stop.
我知道你和阿奇博尔德的事
I know about you and Archibald.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我以为你们只是一时冲动
I thought it was a phase.
没想到你陷得这么深
I had no idea you were in so deep.
英格丽德 他一点都不关心你 他在利用你
Ingrid, he doesn't care about you. He's using you.
他之前追过我 我没上当 你也不应该
He went after me first, and I didn't fall for it. You shouldn't, either.
你怎么撒这种谎?
Why are you lying like this?
英格丽德 你不能跟他结婚 他不爱你!
Ingrid, you can't marry him. He doesn't love you!
仅仅因为你利用男人
Just because you use men,
你只关心你自己
and just because you only care about yourself
并不意味着每个人跟你一样
doesn't mean everybody is like you.
你说的对 他不喜欢我 他是个魔鬼
You're right, he's not like me. He's evil.
他关心我们这类人
He cares about our kind.
他不想我们再躲躲藏藏了 他为我们感到自豪
He doesn't want us to have to hide anymore. He's proud of what we are.
我们要去一个没人能伤害我们的地方
So we're going to a place where nobody can hurt us.
那种地方根本不存在!
Such a place doesn't exist!
如果他们知道我们是什么人
If they find out what we are,
他们总会伤害我们的
they will always hurt us.
如果我们回到我们的家乡就不会!
Not if we go back to where we came from!
阿奇博尔德找到一种回去的方式
Archibald has found a way through.
他在说谎
He's lying.
今晚我们结婚后就离开
We're leaving tonight after we're married.
抱歉 温迪
I'm sorry, Wendy.
工人们说这个地方自建好后基本没变过
Yeah, the workmen say this place is basically unchanged since it was built.
我不喜欢这个地方
Well, I don't like it.
你是怕我们见到鬼吗?
What, are you afraid we'll see a ghost?
我确定我们会见到老鼠
I'm pretty sure we're gonna see a rat.
我讨厌老鼠
I hate rats.
- 你还好吗? - 我觉得我有点醉了
- You all right? - Yeah. I think I'm a little drunk.
我知道你喝醉了
I know you're drunk.
但是我喜欢喝醉的弗雷娅... 她很有趣
But I like drunk Freya... she's fun.
是啊 但是喝醉的弗雷娅有个癖好
Yeah, but drunk Freya has a tendency
就是做很多蠢事第二天又后悔
to do stupid things she regrets the next day.
你在说那个订婚派对吗?
You talking about the engagement party?
我觉得那天你没喝醉
Cause I don't think you were drunk then.
是啊 也许没
Yeah, probably not.
那么...
So...
那天晚上你遇到我之前真的有梦到过我吗?
So, did you really have a dream about me before you met me that night?
这很诡异 是吗?
That's weird, right?
在遇到彼此之前都梦到过对方
We both have dreams about each other before we met.
为什么我们从来没聊过这个?
Why have we never talked about that?
有很多事情我们都没聊过
There are a lot of things we don't talk about.
如果我伤害过你 我很抱歉
I'm sorry if I ever hurt you.
没有 别担心我
Oh, no. Don't worry about it.
- 我很好 - 好吧
- We're good. - Okay.
很好
Good.
刚才说到要结婚的事...
And congratulations on the whole...
恭喜你啊... 我觉得那很好
eloping thing... I think that's great.
- 祝你们幸福 - 嗯 谢谢
- I hope you guys are really happy. - Yeah. Yeah. Thanks.
好啦 我要去看看艾米
Anyway, I'm gonna go check on Amy,
万一她碰到...
in case she runs into any of those...
可怕的老鼠
Rogue rodents.
淡定点 你没事吧?
Whoa. Slow down. Are you okay?
没事 抱歉 我只是有点幽闭恐惧
Yeah. Sorry, I'm just feeling a little claustrophobic.
我们出去吧
Let's get out of here.
求求你... 求你让我走吧
Please... please let me go.
不行 我不能让你走 不会有好结果的
I can't. I can't let you go. It's not gonna end well.
- 我心意已决 - 让她走
- My mind is made up. - Let her pass.
你也许骗得了她 阿奇博尔德
You may have fooled her, Archibald,
但我很清楚你想干嘛
but I know exactly what you're up to.
我只想找一个安全的地方
All I'm up to is finding a safe haven,
这样我们就能平静地生活
so we can live in peace.
我曾经希望你能加入
I was hoping you would join our cause.
我宁愿去死
I'd sooner die.
那好吧
Very well, then.
这下想好好招待我了吗?
Care to do the honors this time?
为什么我们不离开这儿呢?
Wh-Why don't we just go?
她会跟来的 杀了她
She will follow. Kill her.
- 阿奇博尔德 我不能 - 你答应过的
- Archibald, I can't. - You promised.
- 我知道 但是... - 你爱我吗?
- I know, but... - Do you love me?
- 我当然爱你 - 那就杀了她...
- Of course I love you. - Then kill her...
不然我会杀了她
Or I will.
妈咪嘛咪哄
Pila metalli.
妈咪嘛咪哄!
Pila metalli!
雅典娜!
Athena!
亲爱的...? 怎么了?
Sweetie...? What's happening?
我刚才死了
I just died.
温迪杀了我
Wendy killed me.
哇 我们这个周末要结婚了
Wow, we are getting married this weekend.
是啊
I guess we are.
当然啦 我第一次遇见你
Of course, the first time I met you,
我就知道我们会结婚
I knew we'd get married.
- 你才没有呢 - 你在开玩笑吧?
- Y-You did not. - Are you kidding?
我真的知道 真的
No, I-I did. I did.
我走进弯曲手肘
I walked into the Bent Elbow.
我记得那是个星期二
I think it was a Tuesday,
我来到小镇大概一星期了 然后...
I'd been in town maybe a week, and...
你出现了 在吧台后面调酒
There you were, mixing a drink behind the bar.
然后 我...
And I...
我说不清楚 我就是有这个感觉
I don't know, I just had this feeling.
就像...
It was...
就像电波扫过我的大脑 我知道
Like a wave crashing over my head, and I knew.
这样的事一辈子只会发生一次
It's the only time that's ever happened to me in my entire life.
我用尽... 用尽全力才控制住自己
It took... all my strength not to just walk over to you
没有当场走到你面前向你求婚
and ask you to marry me right then and there.
你从没跟我说过这些呢
You never told me that.
我... 不想让你觉得我是个怪胎
I-I... didn't want you to think I was a freak.
你是我的怪胎 我喜欢你这个怪胎
Well, you are my freak, and I like it.
我也是
Me, too.
我从噩梦中醒来 梦里你有危险
I woke up from a nightmare that you were in danger,
我知道那不是梦 那是预示
and I knew it wasn't a dream, it was a vision.
所以我很快赶到店里
So I got to the shop as fast as I could.
但是太晚了
I was too late.
怎么了?
What happened?
你对我女儿做了什么?
What did you do to my daughter?
问你妹妹吧
Ask your sister.
这是个意外
It was an accident.
你杀了我的爱人
You killed my love.
你应该去死 我要把你千刀万剐!
You deserve to die. I'll kill you as many times as it takes!
妈咪嘛咪哄
Cultrum incalescere.
- 爸爸! - 走开!
- Daddy! - Get out of the way!
妈咪嘛咪哄
Cinis Cineris.
发生了什么? 他去哪儿了?
What happened? Where did he go?
- 对不起 - 你杀了我爸爸
- I'm sorry. - You killed my father.
不要想了 让它过去吧 嘘
Let it go, let it go. Shh.
深呼吸 嘘
Breathe. Shh...
早晨之前弗雷娅就会死
Freya will be dead by morning.
她们总是同一天死去
They always die on the same day.
这是意外
It was an accident.
我是想保护她 她想跟他一起走
I was trying to protect her. She was gonna run away with him.
你知道她爱他吗?
Did you know that she was in love with him?
对不起
I'm sorry.
如果你早点告诉我...
If you had told me...
她爱他 那我们就能一起救她了
she was in love with him, then together we could have saved her.
但是 你把他们都杀了
And instead, you've killed them both.
你知道我从没想过伤害她们
You know I would never hurt the girls on purpose.
但是你确实伤害了她们 因为你又鲁莽又危险
But you did hurt them, because you're reckless and dangerous
你总是做事不经过大脑
and you act without thinking.
滚出去
Get out.
我再也不想见到你
I never want to see you again.
就这样
And... that was it.
我再也没见过温迪
I didn't see Wendy again
直到一个月前她出现在我们门廊上
until she turned up on our porch a month ago.
那... 雅典娜怎么样了?
And... what happened to Athena?
她和阿奇博尔德女巫大会里的两个女人
She left town with two women
离开了小镇
from Archibald's coven.
我下了咒 因此她们再也找不到东区了
I spelled them so they could never find East End again.
我跟踪了她很多年
I tracked her for years.
她在1960年初死了
And she died in the early 1960s.
我很爱那个小女孩
I loved that little girl.
我也爱阿奇博尔德
I loved Archibald, too.
那个咒语好真实
That spell was so real.
就像在几个小时里我把所有事情都经历了一遍
It was like I lived through it all again in a matter of hours.
我能闻到感受到所有东西 我就在那儿
I could smell and taste everything. I was there.
但我还是不懂 我为什么这么失控?
But I still can't understand it. How could I have gotten so out of control?
我们内心都有阴暗面 英格丽德
We all have darkness inside of us, Ingrid,
即使是我们中最善良的人
even the best of us.
即使是你
Even you.
伙计们 又有麻烦了
Guys, we have a problem.
这些麻烦还不够?
Besides all the other problems?
避风港的墓穴里有一面墙挂满了枝毒
There's an entire wall of ramus mortium in the catacombs of Fair Haven.
- 一整面墙? - 枝毒是什么?
- An entire wall? - What the hell is ramus mortium?
- 我们该怎么办? - 有其他人见过吗?
- What are we gonna do? - Has anyone else seen it?
没有
No.
我们得抢在别人之前行动
Then we need to do something about it before somebody does.
嘿 宝贝 要吃早餐吗?
Hey, sweetie, want to grab some breakfast?
不用了 谢谢 我得去工作了
No. Uh, thanks. I should get to work.
- 你没事吧? - 没事
- Are you okay? - Yes, fine.
待会儿见
I'll see you later.
- 嘿 - 嘿 宝贝
- Hey. - Hey, babe.
- 你也宿醉没醒么? - 我比你严重多了
- Are you as hungover as I am? - So much more.
- 疯狂的一晚 是吧? - 非常疯狂
- Crazy night, huh? - Very crazy.
嘿 宝贝 我想跟你谈谈结婚这事
Hey. Babe, I kind of want to talk to you about the whole elopement thing.
嗯 我觉得我们应该再等等
Yeah. Yeah, I think we should wait.
我也这么觉得
Me, too.
是啊 如果我们要结婚 那就好好结
Yeah, if we're gonna do it, let's do it right.
我们要办一个真正的婚礼 有家人和朋友陪伴
We'll have a real wedding, with family and friends.
我就是想说这个
That's exactly what I was gonna say.
你看吧? 就说我们是天生一对了
You see? That's why we're made for each other.
弗雷娅?
Freya?
我听到你们要私下结婚?
What's this I hear about an elopement?
事实上 我们会等一段时间
Well, actually, we're gonna wait.
我们会在这里结婚 办一个盛大隆重的婚礼
We're gonna do it here, make it big and splashy.
告诉世界我们对彼此的感觉
Tell the world how we feel about each other.
很好 我很高兴你们选择了正确的方式
Oh, good. I'm glad you're gonna do it right.
你和你的家人对我来说很重要 弗雷娅
You and your family mean so much to me, Freya.
我有一个大计划
I have big plans for you.
一定会很棒的
It's going to be wonderful.
我好激动
I am so excited.